Guide to the Lloyd Richards Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Production Files, 1954-2003; Series I; 27.93; (53 boxes)
  - The Piano Lesson by August Wilson
    - San Diego production, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 302-307)
    - San Diego production, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 308-313)
    - Los Angeles production, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 314-317)
    - Washington, D.C. production, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 318-326)
    - Contracts and rights agreements, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 327-331)
    - Budgets, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 332-333)
    - Production budget comparisons, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 334)
    - Corporate sponsors, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 335)
    - Publicity, 1987-1990 (Box 38, Folder 336-337)
    - Marketing, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 338)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 339-341)
    - Costumes, 1989-1991 (Box 38, Folder 342-343)
    - New York productions, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 344-358)
    - New York productions, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 359-365)
    - Music, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 366)
    - Research report, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 367)
    - Audience survey, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 368-369)
    - "Hit Show Club", 1990 (Box 39, Folder 370)
    - Payroll, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 371)
    - Marketing and media, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 372-373)
    - Postcards, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 374)
    - Study guide, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 375)
    - Tony Awards, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 376)
    - Royalty pool, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 377-378)
    - 1992 taxes, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 379)
    - Touring productions, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 380-382)
    - Touring productions, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 383-387)
    - "Profit distribution", 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 388)
    - Financial and tax documents, 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 389)
    - South Africa production, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 390)
    - CBS Hallmark Hall of Fame teleplay production, 1994-1995 (Box 40, Folder 391-409)
    - Black Emmy awards, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 410)
    - The Christophers awards, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 411)
    - Wayne State University production, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 412)
    - Script and program, undated (Box 41, Folder 413-415)
    - "Miscellaneous", 1989-1992 (Box 41, Folder 416-420)
  - Quasimodo, 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 421)
    Production was likely unrealized
  - The Quiet in the Land, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 422)
  - A Rainless Sky by Neil Yarema, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 423)
  - A Raisin in the Sun by Lorraine Hansberry
    Ethel Barrymore Theatre, New York City; Adelphi Theatre, London, 1959; revived at Yale Repertory Theatre, 1983
    - New York production, 1958-1960 (Box 42, Folder 424-425)
      See also: Oversize Box 168, Folder 1823; Oversize Box 170, Folder 1846-1847
    - Caedmon Records recording, 1971-1988 (Box 42, Folder 426)
    - Documentary, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 427)
    - New Brunswick, NJ productions, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 428-429)
  - The Resurrection of Lady Lester by OyamO, 1981-1982 (Box 43, Folder 430)
    CBS Cable production (television)
  - The Redemption Center by Ron Cowen, undated (Box 43, Folder 431)
  - Richard III by William Shakespeare, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 432-434)
    Boston University, 1967
  - Rip Van Winkle by Richard Nelson, 1981
  - Roots: The Next Generations, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 435-436)
    Part 6 (mini-series), ABC, 1979 (television)
  - Roots: The Next Generations, 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 437-441)
  - The Rose Tattoo by Tennessee Williams, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 442-443)
    Hunter College, 1973
  - Seven Guitars by August Wilson
    Eugene O'Neill Theater Center, 1994; Goodman Theatre, Chicago, 1995; Huntington Theatre Company, Boston, 1995; Walter Kerr Theatre, New York City, 1996
    - National Playwrights Conference, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 444)
    - Casting, 1994-1996 (Box 45, Folder 445)
    - Stage manager reports, 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 446)
    - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 447)
    - Contracts, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 448)
    - Boston production, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 449)
    - New York production, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 450-455)
    - Los Angeles production, 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 456-459)
    - Production folder, 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 460)
    - Drama League of New York Awards, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 461)
  - The Sign in Sidney Brunstein's Window by Lorraine Hansberry, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 462)
    Hunter College, New York City, 1976
  - The Suicide by Nikolai Erdman, 1980
    Yale Repertory Theatre, 1980
  - Summer Tree by Ron Cowan, undated (Box 45, Folder 463)
  - That's the Game, Jack by Douglas Taylor, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 464)
    Tanglewood Writers Conference Theatre, Tanglewood MA, 1967
  - Timon of Athens by William Shakespeare, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 465-466)
  - To Mecca by Athol Fugard, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 467)
    Yale Repertory Theatre, 1984
  - A Touch of the Poet by Eugene O' Neill, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 468-469)
    Yale Repertory Theatre, 1983
  - Two Trains Running by August Wilson (Box 47)
    Yale Repertory Theatre, 1990; Huntington Theatre Company, Boston, 1990; Old Globe Theatre, San Diego, 1991; Seattle Repertory Theatre, 1991; John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts/Eisenhower Theatre, Washington D.C., 1991; Mark Taper Forum, later transferred to the James A. Doolittle Theatre, Los Angeles, 1992; Walter Kerr Theatre, New York City, 1992; Goodman Theatre, Chicago 1993
    - Early script drafts, 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 470-472)
    - Yale Repertory Theatre production, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 473-475)
    - Boston production, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 476-480)
    - Script revisions, 1990 December (Box 47, Folder 481)
    - San Diego production, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 482-483)
    - Seattle production, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 484-486)
    - Casting, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 487-490)
    - Subsidiary agreement correspondence, 1991 August (Box 48, Folder 491)
    - Contracts, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 492)
    - Transportation, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 493)
    - Washington D.C. and Los Angeles productions, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 494-496)
    - Washington D.C. production, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 497-499)
    - Los Angeles production, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 500-504)
    - Various production publicity, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 505-508)
    - Correspondence regarding various productions, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 509-512)
    - Theatre Development Fund, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 513)
    - "Broadcast Alternative Presentation", 1991 (Box 48, Folder 514)
    - Advertising, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 515)
    - Framed artwork, 1991
    - Bonds, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 516)
    - Designers, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 517)
    - Financial, 1991-1993 (Box 48, Folder 518-524)
    - Invitations, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 525)
    - Lights, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 526)
    - Marketing, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 527-529)
    - Press information, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 530)
    - Props, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 531)
    - Set, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 532)
    - Sound, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 533)
    - New York production, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 534-537)
    - New York and Chicago productions, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 538-540)
    - Audience survey, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 541)
    - Tony Awards, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 542)
    - Actors Equity Association correspondence, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 543)
    - Chicago, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 544-547)
    - "Miscellaneous", 1992 (Box 49, Folder 548)
  - Uncle Vanya by Anton Chekhov, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 549-550)
  - Who's Got His Own by Ron Milner, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 551-552)
    St. Clement's Church Theatre, New York City, 1966
  - Wonder Wheel by Jerome Chodorov, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 553)
  - The Yearling by Paul Osborn, 1965-1985 (Box 50, Folder 554-557)
    Alvin Theatre, New York City, 1965
  - You Are There, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 558)
    "Galileo," for CBS (television)
  - "The Bob Hope/Yale Drama School Humor Project", 1988 (Box 50, Folder 559)
  - "Great Lakes Drama Festival", circa 1954 (Box 50, Folder 560)
  - Masters of American Music Series voiceover script, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 561)
  - Untitled spiral notebooks, 1996, undated (Box 51, Folder 562-563)
  - Correspondence concerning audience criticism, 1985-1988 (Box 51, Folder 564)
  - Medal of Honor Rag, 1981-1982 (Box 51, Folder 565-566)
  - "Saginaw" clippings, 1954
  - "Northland Playhouse" clippings, 1956-1957
  - Programs from Yale Repertory productions (Box 52, Folder 567-582)
  - Programs from other Richards productions (Box 53, Folder 583-589)
  - Production posters, 1957-1993
- Professional Papers, 1966-2002; Series II; 26.8; (39 boxes)
  Series II. Professional Papers is organized into six subseries: General Files, Teaching Files, Speeches and Lectures, Awards and Honorary Degrees, Subject Files, and Other Papers.
  Professional Papers includes Richards's files relating to his professional activity outside of productions and his Eugene O'Neill Memorial Theater Center duties.
  General Files contains materials relating to Richards's service on committees, councils, boards, grant panels and his participation in consulting, artist-in-residencies, and fellowships. These files include correspondence, financial documents, itineraries, review reports, travel documents, conference proceedings, and printed material.
  Teaching Files includes correspondence, class lists, notes, grade books, exams, syllabi, and printed materials from the various teaching positions that Richards held throughout his teaching career.
  Speeches and Lectures contains transcripts, notes, and printed materials regarding speeches and lectures that Richards delivered as Dean of the Yale School of Drama, at other universities and colleges, at tribute and memorial services, upon receiving awards and honorary degrees, and at other events. Richards's speeches at Yale were delivered for school openings, commencements, annual reports, addressing the Yale corporation fellows, alumni events, and union disputes.
  Awards and Honorary Degrees includes certificates, medals, plaques, trophies, and other commemorative objects received by Richards. Correspondence regarding awards and honorary degrees is in Series IV. Correspondence; photographs of events are in Series V. Photographs, and the drafts and notes for acceptance speeches are in the subseries Lectures and Speeches.
  Subject Files contains printed materials and notes collected by Richards on specific topics. Other Papers includes writings by and interviews with Richards, notes and notebooks, agendas, address books, Rolodexes, publicity materials, writings of others, and programs for productions that Richards had no involvement in.
  - General Files
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by organization and project name.
    - Afro/American Theatre Total Arts Foundation, 1977
    - AT&T: OnStage, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 590)
    - Alrose Productions, 1993, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 591)
    - American Arts Alliance, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 592)
    - American Council for the Arts (National Arts Policy Center Advisory Committee), 1993 (Box 54, Folder 593)
    - American Foundation for Negro Affairs, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 594)
    - American Playhouse, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 595)
    - American Shakespeare Festival Theatre, 1973, 1975, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 596-597)
    - American Theatre Association, 1971 December 16 (Box 54, Folder 598)
    - American Theatre Wing, 1975-2002 (Box 54, Folder 599-600)
    - Arts Council of New Zealand, 1992-1993 (Box 54, Folder 601)
    - Australian National Playwrights, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 602)
    - Berkeley Repertory Theatre, 1985 January 17 (Box 54, Folder 603)
    - Big Sky Blues, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 604)
    - Black Academy of Arts and Letters, 1970-1971 (Box 54, Folder 605)
    - Black Theatre Alliance, 1974 January 16 (Box 55, Folder 606)
    - Black Theatre Network News, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 607)
    - Bush Foundation, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 608)
    - Cairo International Festival, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 609)
      Includes "The Boatman" script by Sameh Mahran
    - California Institute of the Arts, 1996 January 31 (Box 55, Folder 610)
    - Canadian Broadcasting Corporation (Lloyd Richards Training Program), 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 611)
    - Center for Visual History, 1993-1994 (Box 55, Folder 612)
    - Central Park Center Stage, undated (Box 55, Folder 613)
    - Century Association, 1984-1987, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 614)
    - Cincinnati Playhouse, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 615)
    - City of New York, Department of Cultural Affairs, 1991, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 616)
    - City University of New York (CUNY-TV), 2000 (Box 55, Folder 617)
    - City University of New York, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 618)
      Regards "Black America on stage" symposium and exhibition
    - College of Fellows of the American Theatre, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 619)
    - Columbia University, 1995-1996 (Box 55, Folder 620)
    - Connecticut Commission on the Arts, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 621)
    - Connecticut Public Television and Radio, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 622)
    - Crossroads Theatre Company, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 623)
    - Dartmouth College, 1977-1978 (Box 55, Folder 624)
    - Denver Center for the Performing Arts, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 625)
    - Detroit Council of the Arts, 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 626)
    - Directors Guild of America, 1971-1976 (Box 56, Folder 627)
    - Eatonville Community, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 628)
    - Emory University, 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 629-630)
      Includes "Proposal for Master of Fine Arts, Emory University"
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1990-1992 (Box 56, Folder 631)
    - First American Congress of Theatre, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder 632)
    - Ford Foundation, 1974, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 633-634)
      Regards television production of "The Chinese Prime Minister" and 1977-1978 New American Plays Program
    - Frederick Douglass Creative Arts Center, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 635)
      Regards "Spreading the Word" seminar
    - Freedomways, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 636)
    - Fund for New Performance/Video, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 637)
      Includes "The Innocent are Innocent" script by Tomas Rychetsky
    - Gail Stayden Productions, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 638)
    - George M. Company, 1968-1978 (Box 56, Folder 639)
    - Hall of Fame for Great Americans, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 640)
    - Howard University, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 641)
    - Huntington Theatre Company, 1995, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 642-645)
      Includes information regarding Richards's rental lease
    - Indo-U.S. Subcommission on Education and Culture, 1990-1992 (Box 56, Folder 646)
    - International Theatre Institute, 1971-1972 (Box 56, Folder 647)
    - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1980-1996 (Box 57, Folder 648)
    - Kingswood-Oxford School, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 649)
    - Labor Institute for Human Enrichment, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 650)
      Includes photographs
    - Last Frontier Theatre Conference, 2001-2002 (Box 57, Folder 651)
      Includes material on Richards's award
    - League of New York Theatres and Producers, 1979-1980 (Box 57, Folder 652)
    - Literary Managers and Dramaturgs of the Americas, 1992-1997 (Box 57, Folder 653)
    - London 9-11 Theatre and Arts Festival, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 654)
    - Number not used (Box 57, Folder 655)
    - Lucy Kroll Agency, 1991-1996 (Box 57, Folder 656)
      Regarding Richards writing an autobiography
    - Manhattan Theatre Club, 1999-2003 (Box 57, Folder 657-659)
    - Mashantucket Pequot Museum and Research Center, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 660-661)
    - Massachusetts Cultural Club, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 662)
    - Michigan State University, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 663)
    - Middlebury College, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 664)
    - Nabisco Brands, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 665)
    - National Actors Theatre, 1991-1994 (Box 58, Folder 666)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 667)
    - National Black Theatre Festival, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 668)
    - National Black Touring Circuit, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 669)
    - National Coalition of 100 Black Women, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 670)
    - National Conference on Black Theatre of the Sixties, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 671)
    - National Corporate Theatre Fund, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 672)
    - National Endowment for the Arts
      - "A Report on Theater Education in Colleges and Universities", 1973 (Box 58, Folder 673)
      - Dance Company Grants Policy, 1987-1988 (Box 58, Folder 674)
        Includes printed material on funding dispute between Frank Hodsoll and Congress
      - Directors Interns, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 675)
      - National Council on the Arts, 1984-1985 (Box 58, Folder 676-677)
        Regarding presidential appointment
      - Regards service and National Medal of Arts, 1992-1994 (Box 58, Folder 678)
      - Theatre Policy Panel, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 679)
      - Theater Program, 1972-1979 (Box 58, Folder 680)
    - National Public Radio, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 681)
    - National Research Center of Theatre Arts, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 682)
    - New Drama Forum Association, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 683)
    - New Dramatists, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 684)
    - New Federal Theatre, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 685)
    - New Jersey State Council on the Arts, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 686)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1972-1975 (Box 59, Folder 687)
    - New York State Education Department, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 688)
    - New York University, 19961997 (Box 59, Folder 689)
    - Newark Public Library, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 690)
    - Northwestern University, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 691)
    - The Open Theater, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 692)
      Includes "In My Mother's Autobiographical Sketches" script by Issak Esmail Issak
    - Pace University, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 693)
    - Phillips Exeter Academy, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 694)
    - Praeumium Imperiale Awards, 1988-2001 (Box 59, Folder 695-699)
    - Prince William Sound Community College, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 700)
    - Princeton University, 1989-2000 (Box 60, Folder 701-704)
    - Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 705)
    - Quinzaine Internationale du Theatre Quebec, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 706)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1971-1988 (Box 60, Folder 707-711)
    - St. Mary's College, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 712)
    - Smithsonian Institute, 1977, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 713)
      Regards creation of National African American Museum
    - Steeplechase Films, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 714)
      Regards Eugene O'Neill: a documentary film and includes National Endowment for the Humanities grant application
    - Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers, 1972-1995 (Box 61, Folder 715-718)
    - Sonoma State University, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 719)
    - Studio Museum in Harlem, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 720)
    - Tampere International Theatre Festival, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 721)
    - Theatre Association of Pennsylvania, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 722)
      Regards "An American Journey"
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1973-1976, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 723-725)
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1995-2001 (Box 62, Folder 726-728)
      Includes transcript of TCG's American Theatre magazine's oral history with Richards.
    - Theatre Development Fund, 1970-1982, 1991-2002 (Box 62, Folder 729-732)
    - True Colors Theatre Company, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 733)
    - Twentyone for the 21st, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 734)
    - United States State Department of Cultural Presentations, 1965-1978 (Box 62, Folder 735-738)
    - United States State Department of Cultural Presentations, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 739-740)
      Includes materials regarding African survey trip and 1968 "Diary of an American Theatre Specialist: A Report on Theatre in Uganda, Zambia, Kenya and Ghana"
    - University of Georgia, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 741)
    - University of Michigan, 1994-1996 (Box 63, Folder 742)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 743)
    - Village Foundation, 1999-2000 (Box 63, Folder 744)
    - WGBH, 1968, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 745-746)
      Includes material regarding Horizon-TV
    - Who's Who in Black Canada, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 747)
    - William Morrow and Company, Inc., 1991 (Box 63, Folder 748)
    - Professional biography and resumes, undated (Box 63, Folder 749)
  - Teaching Files
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by institution name.
    - Actors Center, 1997, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 750)
    - Actors Studio Drama School, 2000-2001 (Box 64, Folder 751)
    - Bennington College, 1999-2002 (Box 64, Folder 752-753)
    - Boston University, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 754)
    - Catholic University, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 755)
    - Columbia University, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 756)
    - Hunter College, 1972-1977 (Box 64, Folder 757-759)
    - Hunter College, 1978-1979 (Box 65, Folder 760-765)
    - National Theatre Institute, 1970-1977 (Box 65, Folder 766)
    - Negro Ensemble Company, 1967 June 30 (Box 65, Folder 767)
    - New York University, 1966-1972 (Box 65, Folder 768)
    - Oklahoma Art Institute, 1991-1994 (Box 65, Folder 769)
    - Rutgers University, 1998-1999 (Box 65, Folder 770)
    - State University of New York Purchase College, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 771)
    - Wesleyan University, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 772)
    - "Teaching possibilities", 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 773)
  - Speeches and Lectures
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by institution or organization name.
    - American Film Institute's Salute to Sidney Poitier, 1992 March (Box 66, Folder 774)
    - Association of College, University and Community Arts Administrators Awards, 1985 December (Box 66, Folder 775)
    - Philip Barry, Jr. memorial service, 1998 June (Box 66, Folder 776)
    - Bradley University, 1996 April (Box 66, Folder 777)
    - Chautauqua Institution, 1992 August (Box 66, Folder 778)
    - Cincinnati Playhouse Rosenthal New Play Prize, 1998 March (Box 66, Folder 779-780)
      Includes publication of speech in April 1988 Dramatics magazine and letters from Dramatics to Richards regarding publication
    - City College of the City University of New York Langston Hughes Festival tribute to August Wilson, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 781)
    - College of Fellows of the American Theatre, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 782)
    - Collegiate School's Winter Convocation, 1998-1999 (Box 66, Folder 783)
    - Columbia Pictures Industries Executives luncheon, 1984 November (Box 66, Folder 784)
    - Conference on Cultural Diversity, University of California at San Diego, 1990 November (Box 66, Folder 785)
    - Connecticut Bar Association, 1991 June (Box 66, Folder 786)
    - Connecticut College Tansill Black Box Theater groundbreaking, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 787)
    - Connecticut Commission on the Arts, 1986 May (Box 66, Folder 788)
    - Dyson College Lectures in the Humanities, 1988 November 9
    - Eugene O'Neill Memorial Theater Center Nelson and Aida White House dedication, 1997 August (Box 66, Folder 789)
    - A. Bartlett Giamatti memorial service, 1989 October (Box 66, Folder 790)
    - Independent Committee on Arts Policy Art Table, 1992 September (Box 66, Folder 791)
    - Stanley Kauffman tribute at Lincoln Center, 1986 October (Box 66, Folder 792)
    - Michigan State University, 1998 March (Box 66, Folder 793)
    - Middlebury College, 1992 October (Box 66, Folder 794)
    - New England Theatre Conference, 1983, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 795)
    - The Players Salute to Lucille Lortel, 1985 November (Box 66, Folder 796)
    - Princeton-Yale Club, 1985 March (Box 67, Folder 797)
    - Robert Whitehead Award, 1993 January (Box 67, Folder 798)
    - Alan Schneider memorial service, 1954 May (Box 67, Folder 799)
    - Dennis Scott memorial service, 1991 March (Box 67, Folder 800)
    - Theatre Communications Group National Conference, 1984, 1986, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 801-803)
    - Theatre Hall of Fame induction for James Earl Jones, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 804)
    - Theatre Hall of Fame induction of Ming Cho Lee, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 805)